This is Bandit One starting prep sequence, cleared for takeoff.
这里是l37频道准备好可以起飞
Full engine start.
发动引擎
This is Bandit One. I'm easing her up.
这里是l37号开始脱离路面
- Are we transmitting yet?   - Not yet.
- 开始发送信号了吗？ - 还没有
Rodgers, Orin, how's the perimeter?
罗杰斯、奥伦，情况如何？
It's clear.
咱们走
Bandit One receiving signal. Approaching target vector.
目标区域有信号接近
Transmitting to base now, sir.
开始对基地传送，长官
- The place is secure.   - Good. Now we keep it that way.
- 这地区安全了  - 好，继续努力
- Take the left flank, Hargs.   - Sir.
- 保持线路畅通  - 是，长官
Was that him?
那里面是什么？
I don't know. Let's check it out.
我不知道，咱们去看看
- Talk to me.   - We got the bogey on the run, sir.
- 向我回报！ - 我们被伏击了，长官
Which way?
哪里来的？
Rodgers, which way?
罗杰斯，在哪边？
- Which way, Rodgers?   - Cannot identify, sir.
- 罗杰斯，在哪边？ - 不能确认，长官
Is he jamming our frequency?
难道他们在干扰我们的频率吗？
- Looks like it, sir.   - You're supposed to be jamming his.
- 看来是的，长官  - 应该是你干扰他们的频率？
This is Bandit One, homing in on target vicinity.
这里是空中一号，请帮助我确认目标精确地点
Hightop. Hightop!
躲起来，躲起来
I want you to hold this position. Nobody gets in. You got that?
我要你死守这个位置，不许任何人进来，明白吗？
Got it, sir.
是，长官
Closing to zero mark center.
接近目标了
Still on approach vector.
地面支援
Sir, sir, he's here. The Painter's here, sir!
长官，他们在这里长官！
Damn!
靠！准备摧毁目标
Over target signal.
目标锁定
Target is lit. I'm going in.
目标锁定，去吧
Got it. Locking on. Flares away.
好了，发射完毕。让开!
Too easy, Naish.
太容易了
Way too easy.
太容易得手了
Damn it.
妈的
Training mission is over, and the Painter does it again.
训练结束，成功摧毁目标
Returning to base now.
我们现在返回基地
What are you doing here?
你在这里干什么呢
Wait here. Be quiet.
等着，别出声
Where's your mommy and daddy, huh?
你爸爸妈妈呢？
Okay, come on.
好吧，走吧
Drive.
走吧
Thank you for organizing this in such short notice, everyone.
感谢大家这么仓促前来
As I'm sure you can appreciate, we've had a serious situation...
不过我相信你们一定能够理解的，因为在过去的
...come up over the last 12 hours in southern Russia...
十二小时内，发生了一些非常严重的事情
...which requires our immediate attention.
在俄罗斯南部需要我们关注
General lgor Zaysan...
伊冈．塞辛将军
...an iron fist from the Brezhnev days, Afghanistan, the southern states.
一个强硬人物，活动在阿富汗南部区域
Over the last few years he resurfaced in Chechnya.
过去几年中他在车臣当预备役
He made good use of the rebels, considering he's a Russian.
充分利用那里的叛军和俄罗斯的敌对关系
He put together a new army, new weapons.
招兵买马
And now it seems, quite possibly, a nuke.
现在看来，很可能掌握核子武器
Yesterday, he led a band of his rebels across the Terek River...
昨天他带领一支叛军部队越过塔瑞克河
...and captured the Kamshev nuclear plant.
占领了卡姆凡利夫的核子工厂
Now, three of the four reactors...
那里四个反应炉
...at Kamshev have been decommissioned.
其中的三个已经停运
The fuel rods have been removed from the fourth reactor...
第四个反应炉的燃料棒也被清除了
...but it is capable of going online if it is re-cored.
但是它却可能重新运作，如果有人将它运作的话
This would appear to be a Russian problem, Mr. Tensor.
这看起来是俄罗斯的问题
Please, general, let us make no mistake.
将军，请不要误会
Gentlemen...
先生们，
...lgor Zaysan is a very dangerous man.
伊冈.塞辛是一个非常危险的人物
We have been tracking him for a number of years.
我们追踪了他好多年了
His hatred for the Kremlin has become a complete obsession.
他对克里姆林宫的仇恨已经成了一种强迫焦虑症
What's this?
这些人是谁？
- What are you doing with them?   - They are prisoners.
- 干嘛去？ - 他们是囚犯
They surrendered when we moved into the plant.
他们是看守工厂的
Where are you taking them?
你带他们去哪里？
Exactly my point.
执行我的计划
If he is capable of re-coring this reactor...
如果他能够把这反应炉重新运作…
...he is capable of detonating it.
…他有这个能力
That is to say, potentially 100,000 deaths in an instant.
那意味着，片刻间就可能有十万人死亡
And a few hundred thousand more when the winds...
当风吹过整个地区，将会有数百万或更多的人死去
...send the fallout over an area the size of Texas.
相当于得克萨斯州的人口数了
We have proof he's capable of all this?
我们对于那些推测有证据吗？
Amanda, pull up the Flintov picture.
阿曼达，请显示影像
This surveillance photograph was taken in North Korea.
这张照片是在北韩拍到的
The Asian is John Lee Kim.
这个亚洲人是张立金
He's the ace of hearts in our deck of most-wanted arms dealers.
是我们最想逮捕到的军火贩子
The man with him is Andre Flintov...
和他在一起的男人是安卓恩.弗理塔夫
...Zaysan's second in command.
他是塞辛的副手
Now, it seems that Flintov has plutonium on his shopping list.
好像弗理塔夫也在金的客户名单上
What has Uncle Kim got for sale?
他有什么好卖的？
Fuel rods from a failed North Korean reactor.
燃料棒，来自北韩一度废弃的核反应炉
We have to destroy the Kamshev plant...
我们必须摧毁卡姆凡利夫的核子工厂
...before Zaysan re-cores it.
在塞辛重新启动它之前
- Is the package moving?   - Yes.
- 包裹在移动中吗？ - 是
Will they know what's in it?
那里面是什么东西？
The Americans will have their intelligence, and they'll act on it.
美国人一定会有他们的间谍来救他们
You'll see.
解决掉
We are not in the business of doing Russia's dirty work.
我们没工夫理俄罗斯的麻烦事
It's not just the Russians, there are seven scientists...
这不仅是俄罗斯的麻烦，有民间的
...from the private sector working at Kamshev...
七个科学家在那里工作
...four of whom are Americans.   - How the hell did they get there?
其中四个是美国人  - 他们怎么到那里去的
The Russians hired them to help decommission the plant.
俄罗斯人雇用他们去瓦解工厂的运作
- Are they still alive?   - We're not sure.
- 他们还活着吗？ - 不确定
One of them, Arthur Moffit...
其中一个叫“阿瑟马福特”的
...has stayed in contact with Moscow by cell phone.
通过手机与莫斯科保持联系
Latest report suggests he's managed to stay hidden from Zaysan's troops.
最近的报告显示，他好像想办法逃过了塞辛的军队
So let me get the bottom line here.
那我来说明白点
We've got a nuclear reactor to take out...
我们要摧毁一个核子反应炉
...hostages to rescue, and it's all on us.
拯救人质，而又全靠我们自己
Unfortunately, the Russians have lost control on this one.
很不幸，俄罗斯对此事已经失去了控制
As you know, Mr. Secretary...
如你所知，秘书长先生
...they are not averse to our support in this.
他们也不反对我们在此事件上的支持
What do you propose?
你有什么建议？
An air strike.
空中轰炸
We level the place.
那整个区域
- The hostages...   - Four or five lives...
- 人质…  - 四五条人命相比
...against 100,000. I can accept that.
上百人命还是值得牺牲的
General, we're not able to do a large-scale bombing here.
将军，我们不能进行大规模空袭
- How come?   - The area is too contaminated.
- 为什么？ - 那个区域的核污染太过严重
Unless we do a precise air strike, we risk sending huge clouds...
除非能精确打中目标，否则
...of radioactive dust into the nearby town.
就有向附近村镇扩散大量放射性灰尘的危险
Well, from what I know, these reactors aren't easy to take out.
据我了解，这些反应炉是很难摧毁的
We need to target its weak spot.
我们需要花几个星期时间来讨论才行
What we need is a painter.
我们需要的是一个目标人物（目标定位的人）
- Send in a painter with a Ranger team.   - I agree.
- 派出一个目标人物和一队突击队  - 我同意
They could secure the hostages and choose a precise target.
他们可以拯救人质并确定精确空袭地点
It could get real difficult over there.
在那里情况可能很因难
I have to persuade the president that this plan could work.
我必须说服总统接受这个计划
Do we have any guys with real combat experience?
我们是否有一个具有战斗经验的人选？
No, we need someone who's been through this before.
我们需要一个执行过类似任务的人
This man can do it.
这个人可以做得到
Well, I can't see it like that.
嗯，我不能那样看
I just can't see how you'd look at it any other way.
我就是无法理解那还能怎么想呢
- We had our asses kicked.   - Oh, fuck that.
- 我们输了就是输了  - 去你的
One man don't make a team.
一个人不足为惧
No, he ain't nothing without his high-tech shit.
他要是没有那些高科技支持，就什么都不是
Yeah? I'd like to see you say that to his face.
是吗，你敢当着他的面说吗？
Oh, fuck you. I say what I want to who I want.
去你的，我想说什么都行
Even the captain?
哪怕跟队长说？
Yeah.
对
See, we're a team.
我们是一个团队
We don't hold our piss, even for captain.
我们有什么事不会瞒着队长
Well, all I know is, he beat every one of us.
我所知道的就是他打败我们所有人
That's gotta count for something.
那总不能不算数吧
- What's up, captain?   - We gotta go.
- 什么事，队长？  - 该走了
We got two suits from D.C. Flying in to give us our mission.
华盛顿有飞机来接我们过去
- What, tonight?   - Yeah.
- 今晚？ - 对
Let's go.
走吧
We got a mission.
我们有任务了
They're asking for you.
他们要你去
This is the USS Oakla.
美国海军奥卡拉号。地中海
We're in position and conducting maneuvers.
这里是美国海军奥卡拉号，我们己就位
Will advise upon operation commencement.
等待进一步命令
These just came in from our agent in Dagestan.
这是我们在达吉斯坦的情报人员传送过来的
Anshan lmports, one of John Lee Kim's companies.
他们通过张立金的公司进口武器
The shipment's from Namp'o, North Korea?
货是从北韩的南浦港运出的？
- Do we know what it is?   - Certainly big enough for fuel rods.
- 是什么呢？ - 就燃料棒来说当然够大了
The Russians have promised to keep an eye on its movement.
俄罗斯答应监视他们在那里的行动
And to stop it once the situation's stabilized.
传输结束，他们说是如此
We better have one of our guys keep an eye on it too.
不过我们最好也有一个人盯着点比较放心
It's imperative we take out that last reactor...
在这个货柜到那里之前
...before this container gets there.
我们就要把最后的反应炉拿下
It's amazing.
太神奇了，就是老维克多也没机会
Even old Viktor lvanov's given us his blessing.
但愿他保佑，我们这次能干得漂亮点
Come in.
进来
- Excuse me, Mr. Ivanov.  - Yes, Beslan?
- 打扰一下，伊万诺夫先生  - 什么事？
The prime minister is ready for us.
总理准备好见我们了
Okay.
好的
Amanda, Jonathan, good to see you.
乔纳森，你好,见到你很高兴
- You too, major.   - This is Captain Naish.
- 我也很高兴见到你，少校  - 这位是纳许队长
He leads the Ranger team we're sending in.
他带领我们这次出击的突击队
- Good to meet you, captain.   - I know you've been fully briefed.
- 很高兴见到你，队长  - 我知道你一定准备充分
So you know what you're up against, I thought you better hear this.
不过为了让你进一步了解，还是跟你说明白
It might prove critical. Can you run that for us?
我总是要求比较苛刻，能播放一下这个吗，少校？
Sure. Sergeant.
中士！
The rebels came in and found the others, about five.
叛军就要来了，很快就会找到我们了
Me and Valentina are still in the hospital.
我和瓦伦蒂娜还在医院里
You've got to get us out of here. Please, get us out of here.
你们一定要把我们放出去，求你们救我们出去
They're back.
再见了
That's the voice of Arthur Moffit...
这是阿瑟.马福特的声音
...the lead scientist on the decommissioning team.
解除核工厂运作的科学家小组成员之―
- How do you know if he's still alive?   - We don't.
- 怎么知道他是否还活着？ - 不知道
The rebels haven't even acknowledged that they've taken hostages.
叛军根本没有声明他们有人质
The fact is, we haven't even made contact.
事实上，我们根本没有和他们联络过
And you think they're gonna re-core this reactor?
然后你们认为他们会重新启动那个反应炉
So far, everything points in that direction.
目前为止，我们认为事情正往那个方向发展
Good luck, captain.
祝你好运，队长
Gentlemen.
主要目标是什么？
What's my primary target, the hostages or the reactor?
解救人质还是核子工厂？
Both.
两个都是
If there's a choice, which one takes priority?
如果两者冲突，哪一个优先呢？
What are my orders, ma'am?
我的命令是什么？
The reactor.
核子反应炉
Is that it? You wanna say anything more to me?
就那些话吗？没什么话要对我说的吗？
The briefing's over.
询问结束，任务明确了
Damn it, you can talk to me.
见鬼，你可以和我随便谈话的
I'm still here for you.
我还是一直在支持你的
Look, if you want a psych evaluation, you can read the file.
因为关系暖昧而接受精神测试，还不如被开除走人
You wrote it.
那是你写的
It's still there, the same look in your eyes.
还是那样，你眼睛里还是那种表情
What look would that be, the one you saw in the inquiry?
那个表情是什么意思？是你在质询的时候看见的？
That's not fair.
这不公平
What do you want from me, Amanda, a thank-you?
阿曼达，你想从我这里得到什么，谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
好！谢谢
You cleaned my record.
你为我填写报告，不过…
Means nothing to those people buried in the ground.
这和那些长眠地下的人已经毫无关系了
It wasn't your fault.
那不是你的错
I took the order. I lit the target.
我执行了命令，我指示的目标
That mission was over years ago.
那个任务已经结束很多年了
Those deaths are in the past. Leave them behind.
死者己矣，忘了他们吧
That's a good idea.
好主意
Prime minister, hello.
总理阁下，你好
Have you heard from the Americans?
你收到美国人的消息了吗？
They want a rescue and a preemptive air strike.
他们要用空中轰炸并拯救人质
- They say it is in our best interests.   - Of course they would.
- 他们说这是对我们最有利的方法了  - 当然会这么说
Their newfound obsession has been exhilarating for them.
他们找到新的目标正高兴不己呢
They are asking for us to counter with a ground attack.
他们要求我们地面协助进攻
We can't make that promise.
我们不能答应
Then lie.
对
Let them believe they're in charge.
让他们自己掌握好了
The blame rests on their shoulders.
到时出了事也是他们负责
Has Zaysan found...
塞辛找到了
...what he's looking for?   - It's on its way to him as we speak.
他要找的东西吗  - 正按计划，在送去给他的路上
We must let the Americans take out the reactor.
我们一定要让美国人自己砸自己的脚
I'll tell the president.
我会告诉总统的
That reactor's got reinforced concrete.
那个反应炉有加强水泥壁
Sure there's a good spot to take it out?
你确定那是一个好进入地点吗？
I'll find one.
我会找一个合适的地方的
The spec shows a narrow target area for it to implode.
这个仪器能给空中出击确定精确位置
It's all about minimal damage on this op.
关键是对这个物体的打击降到最低
We go in, locate the hostages, paint the target...
我们进去，确定人质地点
...and then get out before anyone knows we're there.
带走目标，马上安静的撤出
Any questions?
有问题吗？
Yeah. Well, how close on our ass is the air strike?
是的。空军攻击多久会到？
They'll be right on our ass. That's why we gotta make it quick.
方位确定后他们紧跟着就到，所以我们动作一定要快
Well, how hot is it around the reactor site?
叛军如果离得很近怎么办？
A small company of Zaysan's loyalists are protecting his ass there.
只有小部分塞辛的忠实部下在那里防守
The rest of the rebel troops are across the river, 20 miles south.
其他叛军在河对岸南面2O英里处
Captain, this being a stealth op and all...
队长，这次任务这么危险
...we gotta leave Orin behind.
我们得把伯恩留下
You can see his fat ass a mile away.
因为你在一英里之外都可以看到他的大屁股
Go blow yourself, asshole.
你这个混蛋的屁股才那么大
Quit it. Let's pack and roll, people.
好了，咱们收拾上路吧，伙计们
- Jacks here.   - What is happening now?
- 我是杰克斯  - 现在发生什么事？
We're moving forward.
我们开始行动了
The team's on its way.
已经派出突击小组去了
We have a man shadowing the container.
我们另外有一个人在监视货柜车
Our forces are ready to intercept it.
我们的部队已经准备好行动了
Have them hold off until the plant is secured...
让他们等到工厂确保安全之后再行动
...or those hostages are as good as dead.
否则这些人质就死定了
Hey, Hargs. Man, I did some checking on him.
嘿，哈克斯，我可以与你核对一下吗？
Total malfunction in Bosnia.
它可不能乱出错
He painted the wrong target.
如果它把我们定位的目标搞错了
We're talking major collateral damage.
后果不堪设想
Yo, what's your name? What do we call you?
你叫什么名字？我们怎么称呼你？
Yeah.
对啊！
What's your name, dude?
你叫什么，伙计？
If it comes to having to save your ass, I wanna know your name.
如果我们连你的名字都不知道，到时怎么救你呢？
Worry about saving your ass,I'll worry about saving mine.
如果我是你们的话，还是先担心怎么救自己吧
All right, people, let's roll.
好了，准备跳伞
We're losing the signal.
我们正在失去他们的信号
Must be on a real ride.
一定是风太大了
Those are 70-mile-an-hour wind gusts.
他们的下降速度有70英里时速呢
Is there a problem, major?
有问题吗，少校？
I hope not.
希望没有
Ready to deploy chutes on my mark.
听我命令，打开降落伞
Mark.
注意
Chutes open.
降落伞打开了
Off the target.
达到目的地
Well, there's nothing more we can do to help them now.
现在我们帮不了他们了
They're on their own up there.
他们全靠自己了
Painter.
伙计们？
Hargs.
哈克斯？
I took a local reading, sir.
看一下读数，长官
Their comsets are down.
他们都下来了
Well, they were due east of us. So let's pack and go.
我们每个人的仪表都要检视一次
Sir.
好了，走吧
This way.
这边
- Morning, Mr. Secretary.   - Morning, John.
- 早安，秘书长先生  - 早安，约翰
We have a green light, sir. The team's on the ground.
我们目前一切顺利，他们到达地面了
When will the target be lit?
目标什么时候能被定位？
Two hours, at most.
最多两个小时
One of our satellites will pick up the Painter's signal.
我们的一个卫星会接收“定位人”的信号
We have an F-14 standing by off a carrier in the Gulf.
我们有一架F―l4战斗机在海湾的航空母舰上
They're waiting for a go-ahead.
他们在等待命令出动
And the Russians have coordinated...
俄罗斯方面
...a offensive move to coincide with the strike.
协助地面行动
Keep me informed, and keep everything on track.
随时给我消息，监控一切任务发展
- Yes, sir, we certainly will.   - Good luck.
- 是，先生  - 祝好运
Thank you, sir. Bye-bye.
谢谢你，先生。再见
Captain Jack Stevens, skipper of the Oakla.
我是杰克斯.蒂文，奥克拉号的船长
- Lt. Randall, sir.   - Lt. Carter, sir.
- 我是雷纳德中尉，长官  - 我是科纳中尉，长官
Colonel Reynolds gave me some details about your mission.
科纳，雷纳德，我对你们的任务有所了解
In fact, too few.
你们两个其实都很杰出
I was impressed with your flight record...
你们的飞行记录，我很欣赏
...particularly on the F-14 Tomcat. I do see that you're carrier-qualified.
尤其是在F-l4战斗机的飞行任务表现出色。你们两个的素质确实很适合这次任务
But what I don't see is why a Navy pilot can't fly this mission.
但是我不明白的是为什么海军的飞行员不能执行这次飞行任务
The way we see this little get-to, it's an Army problem.
我们的看法是这是陆军的问题
So the Army ought to be the one to clean it up.
所以应由我们自己解决
- Not good enough, lieutenant.   - The dispatch from Col. Reynolds...
- 这个答案不够好，中尉  - 这是上面的命令
...explains the parameters of this operation, the need for secrecy.
不需要向我们特别解释
I don't give a damn about dispatch, lieutenant.
我才不管是什么任务分配呢
If I'm gonna entrust my airplane to an Army pilot...
我要把心爱的战机借给陆军飞行员
...and let him fly in harm's way, then by God, I wanna know why.
任由他们就那么开走，看在上帝的份上，我想知道为什么？
Yes, sir.
是，长官
I know the terrain, I know the ground crew.
我了解那个梦想，我了解地面部队
You could let a naval aviator fly this operation...
你可以让一个海军飞行员来执行这次任务
...but the Army needs me.
但是陆军需要我
- Fair enough, lieutenant.   - Roger that, sir.
- 很好，中尉  - 很高兴你这么说，长官
This looks like the hospital.
数据处理，目标区域。这是关押人质的地方
The reactor's less than a mile away.
反应炉在一英里之内了
Go. Go.
上，上
Moffit says he was hiding in the hospital.
探测人质方位
He's here.
在这里
Got it going again for you, sir.
附近暂时无人，长官
- Great.   - But Harg's set's dead.
- 很好  - 是哈克斯说的
- Damn.   - What do we do now?
- 泰勒  - 我们现在怎么做？
This way. This way.
这边，这边
Go. Go with them.
去，和他一起去
Hargs, stay close to the Painter.
哈克斯，和“定位人”保持近距离
Sir.
是，长官
Rodgers, Orin, upstairs.
罗杰斯，沃伦，去楼上
Hightop, cover the lobby.
海特，到大厅去
I got the morgue.
我去查其他通道
How come that don't surprise me?
那家伙还真让我吃惊
Clear up here.
这里安全
Your nerves shaky?
这里让你感觉不安？
Yeah, a little.
对，是的
Good. Means your instincts are turned on.
很好，那就是你的本能被唤醒了
- I found them.   - Please don't hurt us.
- 我找到他们了  - 请不要伤害我们
Please don't hurt us.
请不要伤害我们
Nobody's gonna hurt you. Come with me. Go on, let's go.
没人会伤害你们的。安静，跟我们走
Go, go, go. This way.
这边走
Go.
快走！
We got bogeys. Three of them, coming right at me.
我们碰到障碍了，他们一起往我这里来
- Who's she?   - Valentina Bakoff, my coworker.
- 她是谁？ - 我的助手
- Where are the others?   - We don't know.
- 其他人呢？  - 我们不知道
There were seven of us working here when the soldiers came.
士兵进来的时候，我们在不同的区域工作
I think they were in the breeder reactor.
我想他们在最新的反应炉那里
- Where were you?   - Working in the cooling tower...
- 那你当时在哪里？ - 我和她在了望塔工作
...with her.  - How did you get there?
- 你怎么到刚才那地方去的？
There's underground pipe ways that connect to the reactors.
有地下管道系统连接这些反应炉
When we got here, soldiers were wrecking the medical center.
我们到的时候，那些士兵占领了医疗中心
- And we hid.   - Who's the woman in the morgue?
- 我们可以走了吗？ - 地下通道那里的女人是谁？
- What woman?   - One with the hole in the head.
- 什么女人？ - 那个扎辫子的女人
- We don't know.   - How do we get through those pipes?
- 我们不知道  - 怎么从管子里通过
Through the morgue.
从地下通道那里的入口下去
Hightop, pull back.
海因塔，撤退
You know her?
你认识她吗？
She worked with us.
她和我们一起工作
Come on.
走吧
Okay, it's clear.
好，没有发现状况
- Which way?   - Left.
- 往哪一边走？ - 左边
Check upstairs.
去楼上检查看看
There's nothing here but a stinking woman.
除了一个恶臭的女人，什么也没有
Let's go see Flintov.
咱们去弗林托夫那里吧
This is it.
就是这里
This is the entrance to reactor number three?
- 这是去三号反应炉的入口  - 对
- You sure?   - Absolutely.
- 确定吗？ - 绝对
Go.
上去
Orin, Hightop, stay with the civilians.
沃伦，躲起来，和那些人质一起
Son of a bitch.
混蛋
Shit, that makes seven.
该死的！真没人性
We're moving out.
我们该撤退了
We can't just leave them here.
不能就这么把他们留在这里
He's right, captain. These are Americans.
他说得对，队长他们都是美国人
I don't like it either, but we gotta make evac. That's five klicks away.
我也不喜欢这样，但是没有选择
We got no time to be carrying bodies.
我们时间不多了
Leave the dead.
把死人留在这里
Let's move out.
我们撤退
You know the right target?
你知道正确的目标是什么吗？
Do you?
难道你知道？
Just do your thing, Painter.
去做你的事吧，“定位人”
Move out, Hargs.
哈克斯，撤退
We have confirmation. The target is lit.
锁定目标，收到定位目标
The countdown starts now, gentlemen.
先生们，行动开始倒数
We have a go for extraction. Repeat, we have a go for extraction.
我们有定位目标，重复目标确定
Prep the chopper on pad five.
把直升机准备好
Yes, sir, we copy. We'll just be waiting for a call.
是，先生，收到。我们就等你的命令了
All right, Helo One, you're cleared for takeoff.
好，你可以起飞了
We'll see you on the other side.
在另一边再见，再会了
Roger that, Mother.
知道了，妈妈
Contact Wingate Field, report status to Colonel Reynolds.
最后一次向雷纳德中尉联络，还是没有联络到，无线电频率受阻
So tell me, how long did you?
还要多久？
Still no contact. Radio silence maintained.
电子通信还没有反应
Evac operation still on schedule.
撤退仍按计划进行
Keep moving. Keep moving.
走吧，快走吧
I told you.
我告诉过你
Stay awake. Stay awake.
保持清醒，保持清醒
How much further?
还有多远？
Marking time on 0345 hours.
现在计时：O3：45
Evac's at 0500 hours.
撤离时间：O5：OO
Painter, don't be late.
“定位人”，别迟到了
Jacks here.
我是杰克斯
- Good morning. How are you?   - Fine.
- 早安，你好吗  - 很好
- And you, Mikhail?   - Waiting for news.
- 你在干什么呢？ - 等消息
- What is happening?   - Less than an hour to evac.
- 现在是怎么回事？ - 他们还有不到一个小时撤退
- But no word?   - They're still under radio silence.
- 但是没有回报吗？ - 无线电信号没有恢复
Look, there's another call I have to take.
我有另一个电话进来
I'll get back to you as soon as I can, okay?
我马上回复你电话好吗？
Okay.
好！
Amanda, you better get in here.
阿曼达，你最好来一下
The target's set and the chopper's inbound.
目标锁定但直升机出事了
This is it.
就这里
Painter, this is Naish.
“定位人”我是纳许
- Painter, this is Naish. Do you copy?   - Roger that, Naish.
-“定位人”我是纳许，你收听到吗？ - 收到
I'm one klick to your rear and closing fast.
我差不多到了，我会尽快赶到
Everything's cool.
一切顺利
Let's break some fucking radio silence.
除了该死的无线电干扰
Raptor, this is Big Bad Wolf. Do you read?
森林狼，这里是大友狼，你收到吗？
This is Raptor. Wolf, what's your situation?
这里是森林狼，你有什么情况？
Piggies assembled and one is on his way.
我们撤退了，还有一个人在路上
- What's his E TA?   - Fifteen minutes, at most.
- 他大约什么时候到达？ - 最多l5分钟
Copy that. What about the prize?
收到，有什么奖品？
Two onboard, five fatalities pre-extraction.
找到2人，另外5个人质死了
- Final approach, Wolf.   - Copy that, Raptor. Over and out.
- 正在赶来，老狼  - 收到，完毕
Get ready.
准备好
Let's move.
行动
Let's move. Get in! Hargs, move it. Let's go, fast.
上，进去！
This is too easy.
这也太容易了
Much too easy.
容易得不敢相信
We got a problem.
我们有麻烦了
- What problem?   - I think we're being set up.
- 什么麻烦？ - 我想我们中了圈套
- What's wrong?   - He thinks we've been set up.
- 有什么不对吗？ - 他觉得我们中了圈套？
- Grenade!   - Grenade!
- 手榴弹！ - 手榴弹！
- Where is it?!   - Get it out! Get it out! Let's go!
- 在哪？ - 出去！出去
It's gonna blow! It's gonna blow!
快走！
Where is it?
在哪？
- Hands up. Don't move.   - Hands up! Hands up!
- 不许动！举起手来  - 不许动！
Stay where you are.
你…不许动
You, don't move!
别动
Stand still.
站着
Jesus Christ. That crazy bitch could've killed me.
上帝！那个疯女人差点杀了我
We are grateful to you, Mr. Moffit.
对，我们多谢你了，马福特先生
Let's keep them alive...
还是留他们
...for now.
… 当活
To work.
…当活口
Hey, you.
你，嘿！
Hey, come on.
走吧！
You. Quickly, move!
快点，走
Still tracking fuel rods.
运送燃料棒的车
Truck is one hour away from destination.
将在一小时之内到达目的地
You're not gonna like this, sergeant.
让你们看看这个
This is what's left of the chopper's operation recording.
这是与直升机联络留下的讯息
This is Raptor. Wolf, what's your situation?
这里是森林狼，你有什么情况？
Piggies assembled and one is on his way.
我们撤出了，还有一个人在路上
- What's his E TA?   - Fifteen minutes, at most.
- 他大约什么时候到达？ - 最多十五分钟
Copy that. What about the prize?
收到。有什么收获？
Two onboard, five fatalities pre-extraction.
找到2人，另外5个人质死了
Final approach, Wolf.
我们最后接近…
And then a minute and 51 seconds pass...
然后从这里是纳许他们被捕
...before Naish and the others were loaded onboard.
前1分51秒的时候开始
What the hell...?
啊！怎么回事？
- Grenade! Get it out! Get it out!   - Where is it?!
- 手榴弹？ - 在哪里出去，马上！
Let's go! It's gonna blow! It's gonna blow!
快走！走
Get out! Move your asses! Move!
出来！出来
What should we report?
我们要怎么向上报告？
The evac was compromised.
撤退失败
Rescue aircraft destroyed.
救援直升机被毁
Personnel?
人员？
Presumed dead.
假设为死亡
Proceed with the air strike.
开始空袭行动
F-14 strike force is on deck, sir.
F-14空中打击力量甲板待命，长官
Weapons are locked and loaded and ready to fly.
弹药充足，可以起飞
All right, let's get 207 and 209 into the air, gentlemen.
好，把2O7，2O9号飞机送上去，先生们
Get off me.
下来！
What happened?
出了什么事？
You were just to watch them and make sure they got out as planned.
你应该仅仅是看着他们，让他们从工厂撤退的
One they left behind may have figured out those plans.
那个最后面撤退的人可能猜出了我们的计划
- Where is he now?    - We don't know.
- 他现在在哪里？ - 我们不知道
If he gets to the Russians, we're screwed.
如果他逃到了俄罗斯，我们就砸了
- He won't.   - But your men...
- 他不会的  - 可是你的人
...have spent half a day looking for him already.
…已经花半天时间找他
Calm down, Mr. Moffit. He won't get to the Russians.
冷静点，马福特先生，他到不了俄罗斯
What about these Americans? Did they make contact?
这些美国人呢？他们联络出去过吗？
No. Valentina made sure of that.
没有！瓦伦蒂娜确保了这一点
We've blocked the frequency in the area.
我们把这个区域的频率都封锁了
I doubt that he'll be able to make any radio contact anymore.
我想他们不能作任何的联络
Put him in with the others.
把他和其他人一起关起来
Move!
走！
Painter, this is Hargreaves. Do you copy?
“定位人”，我是哈得利斯，收到吗？
Painter, this is Hargreaves.Do you copy?
We had a deal. I set you up.
我们有协议的，我帮你们设圈套
I put everything in its place the way you wanted.
我把一切都按照你们的要求做到了
We appreciate your sacrifices, Mr. Moffit.
感谢你的牺牲，马福特先生
You wanna wipe out your Chechen army, fine...
你想扫除在车臣的敌人，没错，但是…
...but I'm not supposed to be here when the place is taken out.
当这里被占领之后，我本不会被留下的
I'm touched by your deep sense of self-interest.
那就是你自己的臆想了
You promised me the money and safe passage.
你答应给我钱，让我安全离开的
You're absolutely right. Safe passage.
你完全正确！把我的意思告诉他
This is Shadow One. We're on course, bearing three mark seven.
这里是阴影一号，我们在3号7度方位
Godspeed, Army.
加油，上帝保佑，谢谢
Our friend in Moscow will tell us if the American makes contact.
我们在莫斯科的朋友会告诉我们，美国人是否联络上
Put guards at the place he targeted.
那个人是否做出正确的定位了
Take everything apart, brick by brick.
他们会把这里一切都毁了，一砖一瓦都不能幸免
What makes you think he will come here...
你为什么觉得…
...and not contact the girl?
…他会回来重新定位呢？
He's American.
那个美国人
He's probably watching us now...
很可能现在正在监视我们
...planning his next move.
计划着他下一步的行动
- We got a problem.   - What problem?
- 我们出了点问题  - 什么问题？
- That's the best you're gonna get.   - It's not enough.
- 这是最清楚的极限了  - 这还不够
We need to know what happened on that evac.
我们需要知道那次撤退中出了什么事
Run it back.
再重来
- Jacks here.   - Try a high filter.
- 我是杰克斯  - 那边一点
- Hello?   - Amanda.
- 喂？ - 阿曼达
It's you. What's going on?
是你，到底怎么搞的？
Listen, we gotta talk this thing through.
听着，我们得把这事说清楚
All right, listen to me. Just you and me...
好吗，听我说。只有你和我
...nobody else. You understand?
别人不能知道，明白吗
You're the only one I trust.
我不知道还可以相信谁
Something's off about this mission.
这次任务很不对劲
I don't know who's pulling the strings there, but I think we're being set up.
我不知道是谁在勒着我们的脖子，我想我们被陷害了
Did you set the target?
你锁定了目标吗？
Yeah, but I'm gonna set a secondary.
对，但是我要设第二次目标定点，
- Amanda?   - Give me that.
- 阿曼达？ - 给我…阿曼达
What the hell is going on?
到底怎么回事？
- Tensor?   - What happened on the evac?
- 你？ - 撤退时出了什么事？
Put Amanda back on.
让阿曼达听
Soldier, talk to me.
士兵，向我报告
Talk to me.
告诉我
I just...
糟糕
I don't get it.
我真是…不明白
We were on the chopper, and we were clear to go.
我们上了直升机，可以安全离开了
Why would they wait until then to try and waste us?
为什么他们直到那时候才拦住我们？
It was all too easy. We just waltzed on in there like we owned the place.
一直都太顺利了，我们好像如入无人之境
Yeah, no shit.
对，怎么可能
And these fuckers played us.
这些混蛋耍了我们
I mean, what the fuck is going on here, captain?
到底怎么回事，队长？
Let's just concentrate on trying to get us out.
咱们还是想想怎么脱身吧
Yeah, right.
对，好啊
Take a look around. I don't think so.
看看周围，我觉得不可能
- He said something wasn't right.   - Did he give you any proof?
- 他说有什么不对劲  - 他给你什么证明了吗？
No.
不
We have to call off the fighter until we figure out what's going on.
但我们要让战斗机暂停行动，直到我们明白出了什么事
- It's not happening, Amanda.   - You heard what he said.
- 不可能，阿曼达  - 你听到他说了
I don't think you're an accurate judge in this situation...
由于你们过去的关系，我认为…
...not considering your past relationship with him.
你现在下这个判断并不准确
- What's that got to do with it?   - You're too close to him.
- 那和这件事有什么关系？ - 你和他走的太近了
Anyone reasonable would see...
你无法理智判断出
...that there is absolutely no substance to what he's saying.
他所说的话真实性
Look...
听着
...when the evac chopper went down, he probably got spooked.
当直升机撤退被摧毁的时候，他可能受了严重刺激了
You and I both know, in those kinds of situations, people's nerves get tested.
你和我都清楚，在那种情况下，人们的神经系统受到考验
- Nerves?   - That is all it is, Amanda.
- 神经？ - 情况就是那样，阿曼达
Mikhail? I need to ask you a question.
喂？我问你一个问题
Please, go ahead.
请说吧
Have you noticed anything strange about this op?
你觉得最近情况有什么不对劲吗？
How do you mean?
你什么意思？
I can't quite explain it.
我解释不太清楚
Does this have anything to do with your call to the Painter?
这和你与杜贝特的电话有关系吗？
- You know about that?   - Your intelligence...
- 你知道那件事？ - 你们的间谍
...is our intelligence today. Remember?
也就是我们的间谍，记得吗？
But I do believe something is strange, as you said.
不过我确实相信如你所说，有事情不对劲
Minister lvanov is beside himself with this matter.
伊万诺夫部长今天早上因为这件事焦虑不安
- In what way?   - After your helicopter was destroyed...
- 怎么？ - 你们的直升机被摧毁后
...I told him there may be a delay.
我告诉他也许你们的空袭行动会延迟
I said it would be a good thing, give us time to intercept the container...
我说这也许是好事，给我们点时间来检查那个货柜
...and justify extreme measure of an American air strike on Russian soil.
弥补可能会对俄罗斯土壤造成极端后果的核子污染
But he look at me as... As if I spit in his face.
而他看着我，好像… 好像我冲他脸上吐口水似的
What are you trying to say, Mikhail?
你想说的是什么？
Look again at the pictures I sent you of the reactors.
你仔细看看我发给你的核子反应炉卫星照片
I'm going to send someone to intercept those planes.
我现在要找人去查一下那辆货柜车
Okay.
好的
Just to let you know, the Russians are setting up to stop the truck.
阿曼达，跟你说一声，俄罗斯人准备要拦住货柜车了
Secondary target, just in case.
安装第二目标定位器，以防万一
Hey there. Just got your e-mail. What is this?
嘿，刚刚收到给你的电邮。这是什么
The nuke plant in Chechnya. It's from a Russian satellite.
俄国卫星拍到的在车臣的一个新工厂
Shitty quality.
照片影像很差
What do you see?
你看到什么？
Am I looking for something in particular?
要找什么特别的目标吗？
- I don't know.   - Okay.
- 我不知道  - 好吧
Hello.
你好
Somebody's been Photoshopping.
有人在拍照片
- Where? Show me.   - This shadow.
- 哪里，指给我看？ - 这里，不论是什么
Whatever's casting it's been erased.
一定是有类似放射性物质的痕迹
Can you check and see if this was covered by one of our satellites?
你能否看看我们的卫星照片是否有拍到它
Sure. We'll see what we have on the date the Russians shot this...
当然，那么我们有这张相片在同一天俄国人拍下了这张相片
...and the computer will overlay the two...
电脑将两张相片进行对比
...and identify any discrepancies.
看能否找到任何的蛛丝马迹
Is that what you're looking for?
这是不是你要找的东西呢？
Oh, my God. The truck's already been there. We're following a decoy.
天哪，那辆车已经到过那里了。我们跟踪的车是伪装的
Get me hard copies.
给我接海军部
You're violating Russian airspace. Stand down.
你现在进入了俄国领空，出去
We have clearance from the Russian government.
我进入这里有俄国政府批准的
That's not what we were told.
上头并没有通知我
He's trying to lock on. These guys are going hot.
锁定目标…警报。来者不善，接招吧
Let's see if he can catch me now.
现在看你是否追得上我
- He's still on our 6.   - I know a few tricks. We'll lose him.
- 他还在我们6岁的时候  - 我不懂你说什么
Going for weapons lock.
现在看谁锁定谁
Almost there.
好，差不多了
Fire fox one, fire fox one.
发射一号导弹，发射一号导弹
Hold on, hold on. Got another.
等等，等等，又来了一个
I see him. Hang on, hang on!
等等，等等
- We're losing power.   - Put your poker face on, Randall.
- 我们正在失去动力  - 把备用燃料连上，速战速决
Just play a little Texas Hold'em.
警告
- He's got a lock.   - Not for long. Hang on.
- 我们又被锁定了  - 不会太久。坚持
That's more like it.
这回可不会…坐稳了
I almost got a lock.
这回你可跑不掉了
Fire fox two.
发射二号导弹
This is Shadow One. Hostiles taken care of.
这里是阴影一号，问题解决
Hello. May I help you?
你好，有什么需要帮忙吗？
I'm sorry, I was looking for Mikhail Beslan.
抱歉，我找马可.比斯林
Mr. Beslan has been reassigned.
比斯林先生暂时停职了
Are you sure?
真的吗？
Any inquiries about Mr. Beslan shouldbe placed with the Ministry of Defense.
任何询问比斯林先生的电话将被转接到国防部
Thank you.
谢谢！
Painter, this is Hargreaves.
“定位人”，我是哈得利斯
I'm in the tunnel. I got bogeys down here.
我在地下管道里面，我发现了些东西
- Yeah.   - Everything is in place, sir.
- 喂？ - 一切就位了，先生
Have they stopped the truck?
他们拦住了卡车吗？
Yes, sir. We have the men starting to open it now.
是，先生，我们的人现在正要开箱检查
- Let me know when they open it.   - Yes, sir.
- 一打开里面就通知我  - 是，先生
Hi. The radiation suits are in the car.
嗨，防辐射器具就在车里
Hargs, stay put. I'll find you.
你待着别动，我会来找你
There he is! Let's go!
他在那里，上
I know where they're being held. Go, go!
我知道他们关在哪里，快走
Give me Jonathan Tensor.
给我接将军办公室
The Painter was on to something, so was Beslan.
“定位人”一定知道了什么
And now he's been reassigned.
所以他现在根据行动准则将自动更新了任务
All right.
那好
Convince me.
说服我
Painter said he thought it was a setup.
“定位人”说那是个圈套
Amanda, that could mean anything.
阿曼达，那什么也不能说明
What if lvanov planned this whole thing?
如果是伊万诺夫搞的鬼呢？
What if he set us up to go in like cowboys, thinking...
如果他引诱我们去那里
...we were taking out a reactor before Zaysan could re-core it...
让我们以为自己是在塞辛重新启动反应炉前摧毁它
...only, it's already been re-cored.
但其实它已经被重新启动了呢？
That's what they're unloading off this truck.
所以他们才会在那里卸下这辆车
What could lvanov possibly gain from something so insane?
计划这么疯狂的事对伊万诺夫有什么好处？
He's a hard-liner.
他是强硬派人物
He's fallen in with the new Russia, but he doesn't like it. We know that.
表面上服从俄罗斯新秧序管制，但心存不满。这我们都知道
Imagine what would happen if we hit a live reactor.
想像一下，如果我们击中运作中的反应炉，会发生什么事
It'd be hundreds of thousands dead.
几百万人将会死亡
Think where the blame would fall, the country that caused it...
想想国际舆论会如何谴责那个导致如此后果的国家
...and the country that allowed it to happen.
以及允许这事发生的国家？
And political control of Russia would be up for grabs.
俄罗斯的政治秧序又会瓦解了
Something has been bothering me from the start.
从一开始我就觉得有什么不对劲
Usually you have to drag everything out of the Russians...
通常我们必须从俄国的盒子里抢食物才行
...but this time they handed it to us.
但这次他们却双手奉上控制权到我们面前
And every bit of it was through Viktor lvanov.
而又全都是通过维克多伊万诺夫的管道
I give you this, it's crazy enough to be possible...
我的结论是，这简直疯狂得有点可信
...except for one small detail.   - What's that?
除了一个小细节  - 是什么？
The Russians stopped the container an hour ago.
俄罗斯人一小时之前拦住了卡车
From the outside, it tested positive for radioactive levels.
从外面检测的结果，是有放射性物质
The specialists are in the process of opening it now.
专家正在开箱检查
Don't look so devastated.
不要感到这么失落
I think your assumptions are reasonable.
我觉得你的推测很有道理
You're doing a terrific job, Amanda.
阿曼达，你的工作表现非常好
Everybody's very impressed.
我们都有目共暗
This is it. They're being kept inside.
就是这里！他们被关在里面
Right there.
就在那里面
We gotta get out of here.
我们得出去
The fighter's about to enter Russian airspace.
战斗机朝俄军基地去了
- How long till we hit the target?   - Thirteen minutes.
- 多久之后对目标进行攻击？ - l3分钟
Still on approach. ETA from target zone: 12 minutes.
正在接近中，预计到达时间还有l2分l2秒
Get away! Don't touch it!
走开，别碰它
There could be static on your hand.
万一被你搞坏了
It could shorten out the target.
锁定的目标就被转移到别处去
Everyone will understand your sacrifice, Andre.
大家都理解你的牺牲，安卓恩
I'll make certain of it.
抱歉！我也造成了其中的一部分
Soon, this pathetic Chechnya will be a forgotten wasteland.
很快，这个车臣将会成为被遗忘的废墟
And our Mother Russia will be great again.
而俄罗斯呢？将会再次强大
The guards are dead. The Americans have escaped.
守卫死了，美国人逃走了
It's time.
也差不多到时候了
Don't worry.
别担心
I will make sure nobody comes here.
我保证没人能进来捣乱的
Pull back. Pull back. Come on.
撤退！撤退！快
We gotta get 1000 yards away from that reactor.
我们要离那个反应炉越远越好
Naish, keep your men moving. I'll catch up.
纳许，让你的人继续撤离
Stay clear of the village hall.
我会跟上，保持联络好吗？
- What are you talking about?   - It's where I lit the secondary target.
- 你说什么呢？ - 我要启动第二目标定位
Who the hell told you to light a secondary target?
谁让你去引导第二目标点了
This mission was off. Primary target was a setup.
这次任务结束了。主要目标点，确定是一个圈套
What the fuck are we standing around here for?
我们到底是来干嘛？
- Our orders were for us...   - To target a dormant reactor.
- 我们的任务是  - 占领反应炉
- This one has a live core in it.   - A what?
- 这是运作中的反应炉  - 什么？
They used the hostages to re-core the third reactor before we got here.
他们在我们来之前，已经利用人质启动了第三反应炉
Dead hostages had edema in their eyes.
那些人质的眼睛就是证明
- The fuck is edema?   - First signs of radiation sickness.
- 为什么？ - 那种现象是放射线造成的第一反映
I hadn't figured it out until I saw...
我是直到撤退被阻的时候才想明白的
...that we were being shadowed on the way back to the evac.
我可不知道，难怪…
Moffit did lead us through like we owned the place.
我们进来时，感觉就像是自己的地盘一样
Look, we played right into Zaysan's fucked-up plan.
你们看，塞辛的计划被我们打乱了
Now, I gotta deactivate that primary core.
现在我要去解除第一目标的信号
No, man. We ain't changing the op because you got a hunch.
不会吧！就因为你的什么预感，就要我们改变目标？
I guess you're gonna have to shoot me, huh?
难道你要朝我开枪吗？
I gotta do what's right.
那么就这么办吧
- I'm out of here, captain.   - Rodgers.
- 我要走了  - 罗杰斯！
Sir, I think he's right.
长官！我觉得他是对的！
Go.
去吧！
There is another container in the truck.
车上是否有个柜子？
Well, get it open.
我们可以打开的
Now acquiring target coordinates. Locking on to signal.
确认目标地点，锁定信号
Target is in that dome right there.
第一目标定位就在里面
How you gonna deactivate it?
要怎么解除它的信号？
Electrical charge shuts it down.
把电池拿掉就行了
Missile gets diverted to the secondary target.
这样就自动转移到第二目标定位点
Well, we're not getting through that.
我们进不去那里的
How much C-4 did you pack up?
你带了多少定时炸弹来？
How long till firing now?
还有多少时间就要开火？
- Six minutes, sir.   - Very good.
- 6分钟，长官  - 很好
Still on approach vector.
上！
Hold this position. I'm going up top.
守住这里，我上去
I can hold them up from here, sir.
我在这里可以拦住他们，长官
Take out the jeep!
快去占领制高点
- How much time now?   - Less than two minutes.
- 还有多少时间？  - 不到2分钟
Missile is armed and hot.
导弹武器准备完毕
What? What the hell you talking about?
什么？你到底在说什么？
What is it?
那里面是什么？
Someone irradiated dead pigs.
死鱼的尸体
It's the container.
装在货柜里
We gotta call off the fighter.
叫战斗机停止
Do it.
快照做！
Missile away.
发射
Too late. The missile's on its way.
太晚了，导弹已经发射了
Oh, my God.
哦，上帝啊
Target is down.
主要目标脱离锁定状态
Secondary is hot.
第二目标定位点启动了
What secondary target?
什么第二目标？
No!
不！
That son of a bitch did it.
那个家伙成功了
You look like shit too.
看什么？你自己也惨不忍睹
Amanda, what is it?
阿曼达，什么事？
That was the Kremlin.Viktor lvanov is dead.
此次事件的主谋维克多.伊万诺夫死了
They're saying it's suicide.
对外宣称是自杀
It looks like he's been set up to take the fall.
看起来他也被陷害背黑锅了
If the missile hadn't diverted, the Kremlin would be in chaos.
如果导弹没有转向，克里姆林宫现在就可要爆炸了
God knows how deep this really goes.
天知道还有多少隐藏的背后黑手
I'll be leaving for Washington in the morning.
我早上就要回华盛顿了
They'll call you in for your account pretty soon.
他们将让你去欧洲驻扎等待命令
Just like old times.
就像以前一样
Not quite the same.
不太一样了
This time you'll have to say you went against orders.
这次你终于可以说你终于没有按照命令作了
I listened to my instincts. So did you.
我听从我的本能，你也是
- They'll investigate my part, I'm sure.   - Yeah.
- 相信我们两个都没能让我放开那一段过  - 去！
Well, when they do...
不过，真到了这种地步
...piece of advice from my experience:
根据我的经验来看，有个建议给你
Don't get too close to the person asking the questions.
不要离得太近，除非那个人先向你提出这个问题
Is that so?
是吗？
Yeah.
对
Because when you do...
因为当你太接近的时候
...then they're gonna have to answer to me.
那么它们就要符合我的标准才行
My flight's not for eight hours.
离我的飞机起飞还有8小时
That's a long time.
那是很长时间啊